var Questions = [
    {
        question: "First question : which one is the bunniest ?",
        wrong_image: "duck",
        answers: {
            right: "That's right ! Bunnies *are* bunnier than ducks !",
            wrong: "Oh Darn ! You missed it ! The answer was the bunny !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Ok, now with question #2 : of the two pictures, which one is the most bunny ?",
        wrong_image: "cow",
        answers: {
            right: "Yay ! You did it ! Cows aren't bunny at all. They just moo all day long.",
            wrong: "Oh No ! You missed it ! The answer was the bunny ! You'll do better next time...",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Let's proceed with the next question : which animal do you think is the bunniest ?",
        wrong_image: "cat",
        answers: {
            right: "Good ! Even though the cat is cuter, the bunny is bunnier !",
            wrong: "Wrong ! The cat may be cuter, but the bunny remains bunnier !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Next on the list : of the two pictures shown, which depicts the best a bunny-related animal ?",
        wrong_image: "snake",
        answers: {
            right: "You did it ! You have chosen the right picture !",
            wrong: "Whaaa ! You really think that one looks like a bunny ? You have serious vision problems...",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Now with a more difficult one... Of the two pictures shown, one represents a bunny better than the other one. Which one ?",
        wrong_image: "lenin",
        answers: {
            right: "Good, good... You didn't fall for the catch : urban legend says that Lenin was a bunny in his spare time... but it's only a legend...",
            wrong: "Hmmm, looks like you're not so good after all ! The answer was the white animal with the puffy tail.",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Let's continue with this one : which image is the bunniest ?",
        wrong_image: "stalin",
        answers: {
            right: "That's right ! Communists should not be mistaken for bunnies.",
            wrong: "Bad ! Bad ! Bad ! You know, you pay more attention, that was an easy question.",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Of the two living things on the screen, which one would you qualify as \"the bunniest\" ?",
        wrong_image: "marx",
        answers: {
            right: "Right ! Even though Marx's beard is all fluffy, bunnies are bunnier than he is. Although is sure is bunnier than Stalin !",
            wrong: "What the... You really think that !? AAARRRGGGHHH... Do you even know who that was ? Karl Marx was NOT a bunny !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Ok, next question... Which of the two animals is the bunniest ?",
        wrong_image: "hitler",
        answers: {
            right: "Good ! You didn't choose Hitler. I'm proud of you.",
            wrong: "Oh great, now you can't even tell the difference between a cute little bunny and the evilest person that lived !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Let's continue... Which one looks the most like a bunny ?",
        wrong_image: "hitler-bunny",
        answers: {
            right: "Yeah, that was a trick. The wrong one was Hitler again, but with bunny ears.",
            wrong: "I asked for the bunniest, not for the Naziest ! You're lucky I'm not a real person, because I would be spitting in your face right now !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Almost the last question... what is the bunniest ?",
        wrong_image: ["cat", "duck"],
        trick_question: true,
        right_element: "bunniest", // The word "bunniest", on the screen
        answers: {
            right: "Ah ! How did you know !? Hey, it's not the first time you play this game, isn't it ? Cheater !",
            wrong: "HA ! You lost ! Neither one of those animals is a bunny, the answer was : The word \"Bunniest\" in the background !",
        },
    },
    {
        question: "Ok, now for the final question... Which one is the bunnyest ?",
        wrong_image: "bunny",
        answers: {
            wrong: "HA ! WRONG ! Since bunnies are all equals, no bunny is bunnier than another bunny ! In your face, you bunny-ignorant person !!",
        },
        force_loose: true,
    }
]
